MARC FREDERIC HERR

C# AND UNITY DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am an experienced software developer and have been working with the Unity engine and C# for over 10 years. I have developed for various areas such as: Automotive HMI prototypes, control of fans and dehumidifiers as well as video games for Windows and Android.

CONTACT

Phone: 0176 - 70948950

Email: fredericherr@aol.com

Address: Masurenstr. 10, 57299 Burbach,

Germany

SKILLS

- C#
- Unity-Engine
 - Web, App and Standalone
- Java Script (basic)
- Arduino IDE (basic)
- ASP.Net Core (basic)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science - Games Programming

SAE Institute Cologne • 2014-2017

ITA - Information technology assistant

Berufskolleg Technik Siegen • 2011-2014

EXPERIENCE

CEO & Software Developer

ELMEKO GmbH & Co. KG · Sep 2023 - recent

- Human resources management
- Develop Web and Windows Software

CEO & Software Developer

Forgotten Byte UG • Aug 2021 - recent

- Develop and publish own games
- Develop Automtive HMI for various car manufacturers and suppliers

Software Developer

ELMEKO GmbH & Co. KG • Oct 2021 - Sep 2023

- Develop web apps for product presentations
- Develop windows and android apps for fan and dehumidifier control

Software Developer

Humain GmbH • 2016 - 2021

 Develop Automtive HMI for various car manufacturers and suppliers

Links





LANGUAGES

- German Native
- English Proficient